What was it like for you guys, especially after you lose Dylan and now you're down two big ball handlers with him and Fox, what was the challenge like there and how do you think you guys handled it?
在你们失去Dylan之后，现在又少了两个主要的控球手（他和Fox），这种情况下比赛的挑战是什么？你们觉得自己处理得怎么样？
No, well, we got to help our ball handlers more and take care of the ball.
我们必须更多地帮助我们的控球手，并且保护好球权。
Obviously, without Darren, it's going to lend itself to turnover issues, but are there other factors that you guys can shore up to try to cut down on?
显然，没有Darren的话，失误问题会增多，但还有其他方面是你们可以加强来减少失误的吗？
Yeah, of course, just consistency throughout the game in our game plan. I can think of a few down moments for myself, especially in the fourth quarter.
是的，当然，就是整场比赛都要保持执行我们战术的一致性。我自己能想起几个低谷时刻，尤其是在第四节。
Victor, you and Harnstein had some huge battles on the glass there. He was able to win a lot of those, but what was that battle like for you and what do you think you guys can do better to not lose that way?
Victor，你和Hartenstein在篮板上进行了几次激烈的对抗。他赢下了很多，但那场对抗对你来说是什么感觉？你们觉得能做什么来改善？
As I just said, it's all in the scouting. I have to trust the scouting. We have to trust it and do our work early. It's a straight effort.
就像我刚才说的，一切都在赛前侦察里。我必须信任侦察报告。我们必须信任它，并且早早地做好功课。这就是纯粹的努力。
Victor, what would you say is the most frustrating thing about tonight's loss?
Victor，你觉得今晚这场失利最让人沮丧的是什么？
I would say it's spending so much energy on catching back up to the score and then let it go away.
我想是花费了大量精力去追分，然后又让领先或差距溜走。
When you say it's straight effort, is it that simple or are there some tactical, strategic kind of adjustments you can make?
你说这是纯粹的努力，是这么简单吗？还是可以在战术和策略上做一些调整？
What I mean is straight effort is the tactics, we all know it by heart, but it doesn't mean it's easy and we have to work through it.
我的意思是，纯粹的努力就是执行战术，我们都烂熟于心，但这并不容易，我们必须努力去做到。
What did you think of Steph's performance tonight and the way that he played through physicality?
你如何看待Steph今晚的表现，以及他在身体对抗下坚持比赛的方式？
His competitiveness is unmatched. We definitely need it. He gets us out of a lot of tough situations.
他的竞争力无人能及。我们非常需要这一点。他帮我们摆脱了很多困难局面。
Deirin is the one that controls the offense and settles you guys down a lot of the time. You don't have him, you don't have Dylan. What do you try to do to keep things organized, controlled and settled down?
De'Aaron是那个掌控进攻、经常让你们冷静下来的人。现在没有他，也没有Dylan，你们要怎么做才能保持进攻的组织性、控制力和稳定？
We didn't do a great job at it today, but we need some points for sure, taking care of the ball, helping the main ball handlers and being aggressive just like we were in the third quarter.
我们今天在这方面做得不够好，但我们肯定需要更重视保护球权、帮助主要控球手，并且像我们在第三节那样保持 агрессивность（进攻积极性）。
Victor, when it comes to carding Shea, obviously you guys did a really good job of that in game one.
Victor，关于防守Shai（SGA），你们在G1做得非常好。今晚他得分更多了，在想要限制他得分和明白他是个优秀球员、无论如何都会进球之间，你们如何平衡？
Yeah, he makes shots but nothing that he hasn't made all season so we worked on it and we just didn't apply as much.
是的，他会投进一些球，但这些球他整个赛季都在投。我们做了准备，只是今晚没有完全执行到位。
Victor, I have an impression tonight. A big advantage they have is the depth of the bench. I look at the numbers tonight. 57 points in a row apart from their bench.
Victor，我今晚有一个印象。他们的一大优势是板凳深度。看今晚的数据，他们的替补贡献了57分。
How do they do that? At that moment, they take fire like that, where they can always have a guy who's able to score.
他们是怎么做到的？在那个时刻，他们能突然爆发，总有人能站出来得分。
We need consistency. The depth of the bench is one of our strengths. We can't play fast, but we can't play fast if we don't defend, if we lose the ball.
我们需要一致性。板凳深度是我们的优势之一。但如果我们不防守、丢球，我们就无法快速打球。
It's them who take advantage of that and it's a common strength for other teams but it's them who have had the advantage on that field today.
是他们在利用这一点，这对很多球队来说都是优势，但今天是他们在这方面占了上风。
Hartenstein defended very physically on you tonight, sometimes even at the limit of the rules.
Hartenstein今晚对你的防守非常具有身体对抗性，有时甚至到了规则边缘。你如何保持专注，不让自己出离比赛？作为球队和你个人，你们是怎么应对这种对抗的？
We need to learn from all this energy. It's not different from the 13 games of the playoffs. It's not different from the 12 first games.
我们需要从这些能量中学习。这和季后赛前13场比赛没有区别，和前面12场也没有区别。